A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of Economic Development, 1986-1993.
Library of Virginia
- Records, 1990-1993 (Accession 34595)., Extent: 62 cubic feet (62 boxes). (Box 1-62)
  - Tracking Letters.
    - Professional and Occupational Regulation, Dept. of (608-6303), 1990-1994. (Box 21)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (2808-3583), 1990-1994. (Box 22)
    - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (3676-7004, 1990-1994. (Box 23)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (2799-5460), 1990-1994. (Box 24)
    - Virginia Employment Commission (5502-6198), 1990-1994. (Box 25)
    - Housing and Community Development - Housing Partnership Fund constituent correspondence, 1990-1994. (Box 25)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of (3469-4319), 1990-1994. (Box 26)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of (453-3468), 1990-1994. (Box 27)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of (4743-5660), 1990-1994. (Box 28)
    - Economic Development, Dept. of (5662-6616), 1990-1994. (Box 29)
  - Governor's Office.
    - General correspondence, 1990 June-1992 Apr. (Box 30)
    - Administrative highlights and accomplishments, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - African Trade Mission, 1992 June. (Box 30)
    - Beyer Commission on Economic Recovery, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Beyer Commission on Poverty, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Business Modnernization, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Cabinet meetings, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Comprehensive Communication Campaign, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Comprehensive Economic Development Adjustment and Assistance Act, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Congressional Representative's correspondence, 1990-1992. (Box 51)
    - Council on Competitiveness, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Development Report Card for the States, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Ebony Magazine, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Economic and Budget Outlook, 1992. (Box 52)
    - Economic Conversion / Adjustment Committee, 1990-1993. (Box 51)
    - Economic depressed areas, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Ecomonic recovery, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Economic Task Force, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Elko Tract, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Ethics, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Excellence at Work, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - General Assembly Studies, 1990. (Box 53)
    - Global Leaders of the South, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Goals and objectives, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Governor's Economic Development Advisory Board, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Governor's Fellows Program, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Governor's Fellows Speech, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Governor's International Economic Initiatives, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Governor's speaking events, 1990 Jan-1991 May. (Box 30)
    - Governor's speeches, 1990 Sept-1991 Apr. (Box 30)
    - Green index, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Innovation in state and local government, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Intern Program, 1991 Fall. (Box 53)
    - Intern Program, 1992. (Box 53)
    - International Internship Program, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - International Office Survey, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) - Study Reviews, 1990-1992. (Box 53)
    - Local Government Advisory Council, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - London, Brussels, Frankfurt Trade Mission, 1991 June. (Box 30)
    - Long-Term Economic Development Stategy Plan, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Managing with Excellence, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Memos to the Governor, 1990 Sept-1992 Mar. (Box 30)
    - Mid-Year Assessment, 1990-1993. (Box 53)
    - Secretary of Economic Developoment - Studies, 1990-1993. (Box 52)
    - Taipei Trade Mission, 1991 June-July. (Box 30)
  - Special Projects.
    - Oregon Workforce Literature legislation, 1990-1993. (Box 36)
    - Virginia Center Stage, 1990-1993. (Box 36)
    - Workforce 2000, 1990-1993. (Box 36)
    - Project Streamline, 1990-1993. (Box 37)
    - Project Streamline, 1990-1991. (Box 41)
    - Partnerships for Excellence, 1990. (Box 38)
    - Economic Development Policy Statement, 1992. (Box 39)
    - Southern Growth Policy Board, 1990. (Box 41)
    - Dept. of World Trade merger, 1990. (Box 39)
  - Speeches.
    - Speeches, 1992 July-Dec. (Box 43)
    - Speeches, 1993 Jan-Feb. (Box 44)
    - Speeches, 1993 Mar. (Box 43)
    - Speeches, 1993 Apr. (Box 43)
    - Speeches, 1993. (Box 43)
  - Subject Files.
    - Economy Task Force, 1990-1991. (Box 44)
    - Report to Top Management, 1992. (Box 44)
    - SEUS-Korea, 1992. (Box 44)
- Records (Accession 35483), 1990-1993., Extent: 3 cubic feet (3 boxes). (Box 1-3)
  - African Trade Summit / African Heads of State Summit.
    - Briefing Books - African Ambassadors and Heads of State, 1993. (Box 1)
    - Briefing Book - African Ambassadors and Heads of State, 1993. (Box 2)
    - Briefing Book - African Countries and Southern States, 1993. (Box 2)
    - Briefing Book - Focus Groups and Tours, 1993. (Box 2)
    - Briefing Book - Southern Governors' Association Annual Conference, 1993 Sept. (Box 2)
    - Briefing Book - Gabon (Republic of Senegal), 1993. (Box 3)
    - Briefing Book - African Trade Summit, 1993. (Box 3)
    - Briefing Book - Africa Briefing Materials: Regional and Country Analysis, 1993. (Box 3)
    - Briefing Book - Africa Briefing Materials: Regional Analysis (v. 1), 1993. (Box 3)
    - Briefing Book - Africa Briefing Materials: Country Analysis (v. 2), 1993. (Box 3)
    - Briefing Book - Africa Briefing Materials: Country Analysis (v. 3), 1993. (Box 3)
- Records (Accession 35643), 1992-1993., Extent: 2 cubic feet (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  These records were created or collected during the administration of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994, though some records may pre-date this time frame. During the Wilder Administration, Lawrence Framme, III, served as Secretary of Economic Development, 1990-1992, and Cathleen Magennis served as Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1993-1994. These records include information on the proposed Redskin Stadium and development of Potomac Yard; Phoenix World City Project; and Lego World.
  - Redskins Stadium / Potomac Yard Development.
    - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Factual information, 1992. (Box 1)
    - RFP Corp / VRS Analysis, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Alternative site locations, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Presentation to Senate Finance and House Appropriations, 1992 Aug. (Box 1)
    - Letters impacting the stadium, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Hearings, 1992. (Box 1)
    - House Appropriations hearing, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Financial Analysis of RFP Corp / Potomac Yard Development - Summary of Economic Benefits, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Alexandria Mayor / Citizens meeting, 1992 July. (Box 1)
    - Transportation, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Legislation authority, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Call in show, 1992 Aug. (Box 1)
    - Press clippings, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Public information, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992. (Box 1)
    - Potomac Yard, 1992. (Box 1)
  - Phoenix World City Project.
    - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 2)
    - Briefing book, 1993. (Box 2)
  - Lego World.
    - General correspondence, 1992. (Box 2)
    - , 1992-1993. (Box 2)
    - Media / Press Corps, 1992-1993. (Box 2)
    - Secretary Framme correspondence, 1992. (Box 2)
    - Meeting, 1992 Nov. (Box 2)
    - Reports, 1992-1993. (Box 2)
    - Correspondence with Lego officials, 1992-1993. (Box 2)
    - Site analysis, 1992-1993. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Resources Authority.